Lines are meant to be crossed.
Beast of Burden is a action, crime, drama film directed by Jesper Ganslandt.
Sean Haggerty only has an hour to deliver his illegal cargo.
An hour to reassure a drug cartel, a hitman, and the DEA that nothing is wrong.
An hour to make sure his wife survives.
And he must do it all from the cockpit of his Cessna.
Sean Haggerty, played by Daniel Radcliffe.
Bloom, played by Pablo Schreiber.
Jen, played by Grace Gummer.
Mallory, played by Robert Wisdom.
Octavio Hernandez, played by David Joseph Martinez.
Pablo, played by Cesar Perez.
Beast of Burden is a 2018 American crime action film directed by
Jesper Ganslandt and written by Adam Hoelzel.
It stars Daniel Radcliffe, Grace Gummer, Robert Wisdom, and Pablo Schreiber, and follows an ex-Air Force pilot who
must deliver cocaine across the Mexico–United States border for his final run as a drug smuggler.
The film was simultaneously released in limited theaters and on VOD in the
United States on February 23, 2018, by Momentum Pictures.
The film explores themes of smuggling (contraband),
hitman, drug cartel, cessna, dea.
The tone is emotional and intense.